<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<i18n baseKey="m.catalog.document.shop" lcid="en_GB">
	<key id="edition-form-title">shop properties</key>
	<key id="document-name">shop</key>
	<key id="label">label</key>
	<key id="description">description</key>
	<key id="topic">related topic</key>
	<key id="topshelf">shelves</key>
	<key id="topshelf-help">List of top-level shelves that will be online in the shop.</key>
	<key id="shippingzone">shipping zone</key>
	<key id="billingzone">billing area</key>
	<key id="currencycode">currency</key>
	<key id="currencyposition">symbol position</key>
	<key id="currencyposition-help">position of the currency symbol when displaying an amount, for instance: to the right 19.99 €, to the left € 19.99. </key>
	<key id="displaypricewithtax">display price incl. taxes</key>
	<key id="displaypricewithouttax">display the price excl. taxes</key>
	<key id="defaultdetailvisual">default product visual element</key>
	<key id="defaultdetailvisual-help">When no visual element is available for the product, this visual element will be used to display the product details. If left empty, the default visual element for products set in the preferences of the Catalogue and Shop modules will be used.</key>
	<key id="defaultlistvisual">default product visual element (list mode)</key>
	<key id="defaultlistvisual-help">When no visual element is available for the product, this visual element will be used to display the product in the lists. If left empty, the default visual element for products set in the preferences of the Catalogue and Shops module will be used.</key>
	<key id="displayoutofstock">display out of stock products</key>
	<key id="displayoutofstock-help">Allows the display of products on the website when they are out of stock.</key>
	<key id="alloworderoutofstock">allow ordering of out of stock products</key>
	<key id="alloworderoutofstock-help">If checked, customers will be allowed to order products that are out of stock. This field is only available if display of out of stock products is activated.</key>
	<key id="published-product-count">published product count</key>
	<key id="nbproductperpage">number of products per page</key>
	<key id="nbproductperpage-help">The default number of products per page in the shop's product lists in frontoffice.</key>
	<key id="enablecomments">enable comments</key>
	<key id="availabilityalertsduration">availability alerts duration</key>
	<key id="availabilityalertsduration-help">Time during which a new availability alert will stay active.</key>
	<key id="billingzone-help">"zone" document of the "Zones" module that will be used to validate the billing addresses during the ordering process.</key>
	<key id="botaxzone">entering backoffice prices incl. taxes</key>
	<key id="botaxzone-help">Select a tax area to enable entering prices incl. taxes in backoffice.</key>
	<key id="codereference">reference code</key>
	<key id="currencycode-help">Currency used by the shop. It comes from a static list in the "Lists" module.</key>
	<key id="defaulttaxzone">shop tax area</key>
	<key id="defaulttaxzone-help">Tax area used by default for the shop</key>
	<key id="displaypricewithouttax-help">If set to "yes", the price excl. taxes will be displayed on the websites (this option can be used in addition to Display the price incl. taxes).</key>
	<key id="displaypricewithtax-help">If set to "yes", the price incl. taxes will be displayed on the websites (this option can be used in addition to Display the price excl. taxes).</key>
	<key id="enableavailabilityalerts">activate the availability alerts</key>
	<key id="enableavailabilityalerts-help">Activates or deactivates the possibility for visitors to place an alert on the availability of a product</key>
	<key id="enablecaptchaforalerts">activate the CAPTCHA on alerts</key>
	<key id="enablecaptchaforalerts-help">When activating the CAPTCHA, it will be shown to non logged-in users, logged-in users will not see it.</key>
	<key id="enablecomments-help">enable or disable comments on products</key>
	<key id="enablepricealerts">activate the price drop alerts</key>
	<key id="enablepricealerts-help">Activates or deactivates the possibility for visitors to place an alert on the price drop of a product.</key>
	<key id="endpublicationdate">publication end</key>
	<key id="endpublicationdate-help">Date from which the shop will no longer be publishable.</key>
	<key id="isdefault">default shop</key>
	<key id="isdefault-help">There can only be one default shop per website and per language for a given period of time.</key>
	<key id="label-help">text field used both on the websites and in the administration interface to identify the shop.</key>
	<key id="mount-parent">parent container</key>
	<key id="mount-parent-help">Website or website topic in which the system topic associated with the shop will be created. Usually, this is the website in which the shop is put online.</key>
	<key id="orderprocessclassname">Ordering process</key>
	<key id="orderprocessclassname-help">Ordering process to use.</key>
	<key id="pagedescription">page description</key>
	<key id="pagedescription-help">The page description used in the meta tags of the shop homepage.</key>
	<key id="pagekeywords">page keywords</key>
	<key id="pagekeywords-help">The page keywords used in the meta tags of the shop homepage.</key>
	<key id="pagetitle">page title</key>
	<key id="pagetitle-help">The page title used in the meta tags of the shop homepage.</key>
	<key id="pricealertsduration">duration of the price drop alerts</key>
	<key id="pricealertsduration-help">The time during which a new price drop alert stays active.</key>
	<key id="startpublicationdate">publication start</key>
	<key id="startpublicationdate-help">The date from which the shop will be publishable.</key>
	<key id="website">website</key>
</i18n>