<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<i18n baseKey="m.catalog.document.product" lcid="en_GB">
	<key id="edition-form-title">product sheet properties</key>
	<key id="document-name">product sheet</key>
	<key id="codereference">reference code</key>
	<key id="codereference-help">A text field used in the product detail display on the websites, as well as in the orders to uniquely identify the product (the EAN code, for instance)</key>
	<key id="price">price</key>
	<key id="parent-shelf">shelf</key>
	<key id="labelforurl">label in URL</key>
	<key id="additionnalvisual">additional visual elements</key>
	<key id="additionnalvisual-help">The additional visual elements used in the details display of a product to offer more views of the product.</key>
	<key id="articleid">item</key>
	<key id="articleid-help">The item to be chosen from the resources.</key>
	<key id="brand">brand</key>
	<key id="brand-help">Optional document of type "brand" from the "Brands" module.</key>
	<key id="brandlabel">brand</key>
	<key id="brandlabel-help">brand</key>
	<key id="codesku">SKU code</key>
	<key id="codesku-help">A unique stock identifier.</key>
	<key id="crossselling">crossed products</key>
	<key id="crossselling-help">list of crossed products (cross-selling)</key>
	<key id="description">description</key>
	<key id="description-help">A rich text field used in the product detail display on the websites (characteristics, …).</key>
	<key id="endpublicationdate">publication end date</key>
	<key id="endpublicationdate-help">The date from which the product will be automatically unpublished. When it is left empty, the product will never be automatically unpublished.</key>
	<key id="label">label</key>
	<key id="label-help">A text field used in the administration interface and on the websites to identify the product.</key>
	<key id="pagedescription">page description</key>
	<key id="pagedescription-help">Some content that can be used as a substitute in the "Page title" and "Description" fields for pages that contain the "Product details" display block.</key>
	<key id="pagekeywords">page keywords</key>
	<key id="pagekeywords-help">Some content that can be used as a substitute in the "Keywords" field for pages that contain the "Product details" display block.</key>
	<key id="pagetitle">page title</key>
	<key id="pagetitle-help">Some content that can be used as a substitute in the "Page title" and "Description" fields for pages that contain the "Product details" display block.</key>
	<key id="pictogram">pictograms</key>
	<key id="pictogram-help">visual elements used in the product details display as small pictograms showing, for instance, a special offer, a new item, etc.</key>
	<key id="shelf">shelves</key>
	<key id="shelf-help">The list of the shelves of the "Catalogue and Shops" module in which the products will appear. When this list contains more than one shelf, the product is "multi-shelf"</key>
	<key id="shippingmodeid">Special transporter</key>
	<key id="shippingmodeid-help">Field of type "Shipping method" that allows forcing a specific shipping method for the product.</key>
	<key id="startpublicationdate">publication start date</key>
	<key id="startpublicationdate-help">Date from which the product will automatically be published. When left empty, the product will be published until the end publication date (except for manual interventions from the administrator).</key>
	<key id="stockalertthreshold">stock alert threshold</key>
	<key id="stockalertthreshold-help">Value of the stock quantity below which an "Alert regarding stock" notification (Notifications &gt; Catalogue and shops &gt; Alert regarding stock) will be sent to the recipients set in the "Catalogue and shops" module preferences ("Recipients of alerts regarding stock" field). When left empty, no alerts regarding stock will be sent.</key>
	<key id="stocklevel">stock level</key>
	<key id="stockquantity">quantity in stock</key>
	<key id="stockquantity-help">When this field is left empty, stock will not be managed for the product - it will be considered as always in stock. Once filled, it represents the stock quantity of the product. Depending on the shop settings, when this stock quantity reaches zero, the product may be automatically withdrawn from sale.</key>
	<key id="visual">visual element</key>
	<key id="visual-help">Visual element from the RBS Change media store that matches the product's default visual element. It will be used in the "list of products" display on the website, and also in the product details. This visual element will be automatically re-sized by RBS Change when displayed to match the website graphic charter.</key>
</i18n>